LUKE ANTONYSHYN

Computer Science Graduate, M.Sc., B.A.Sc.

@ lukantonyshyn@gmail.com

♥ Toronto, Ontario, Canada

% lanton97.github.io/

github.com/lanton97

SUMMARY

Recent graduate from a research MSc in computer science with a focus on deep reinforcement learning and mobile robotics. Proven track record working independently and cooperatively in academia, publishing one manuscript as a co-first author and completing two additional first author manuscripts. Possesses industry experience, working on a large multi-national team to develop software for complex embedded systems.

EDUCATION

MSc, Computer Science with Field of Study in Artificial Intelligence

Queen's University, Kingston, Ontario

- M Sep. 2020-Oct. 2022
- · Research focus on deep reinforcement learning for control in robotics
- · Performed literature reviews, identified directions for investigation, developed and evaluated novel algorithms for DRL in controls

B.A.Sc. Computer Engineering Queen's University, Kingston, Ontario

May 2020 Sep. 2015 - May 2020

PROJECTS AND PUBLICATIONS

Multiple Mobile Robot Task and Motion Planning: A Survey

ACM Surveys

DOI: https://doi.org/10.1145/3564696

₩ Feb. 2023

Deep Model-Based Reinforcement Learning for Sample Efficient Predictive Control

MSc Thesis

₩ Oct. 2022

Deep Multi-Agent Reinforcement **Learning-Based Formation Control**

Course Project Project Link

Two Additional Manuscripts In The **Process Of Being Published**

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Research Assistant

Royal Military College

Feb. 2023-Present

♥ Kingston, Ontario, Canada

- Contract to develop neural network approach to sensor fusion and localization.
- Responsibilities include developing algorithms, running experiments, and writing a paper.

Teacher's Assistant

Queen's University

m Sept. 2020-Aug. 2022

♥ Kingston, Ontario, Canada

- · Assisted in teaching responsibilities in classes on image processing and computer vision, and reinforcement learning.
- · Responsibilities included grading tests, exams, and assignments, holding tutorials, responding to students queries about course material, and developing new assignments.

Embedded Systems Engineer Intern

Honeywell Aerospace

May 2018 - August 2019

◆ Ottawa, Ontario, Canada

- Developed, maintained and documented system applications for handling central system control, built-in tests, system configuration, and physical environment monitoring and control for a satellite communications system for airplanes.
- Developed and maintained internal tools for sanity testing and customization of external configuration devices for the system.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

C/C++ Python Scikit-Learn

TensorFlow

Linux

Deep Learning

Reinforcement Learning



INTERESTS

- · Reinforcement Learning.
- Deep Learning.
- Multi-agent systems and learning.